<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!-- New document created with EditiX at Fri Nov 11 10:14:04 CET 2011 -->

<CityDialog>
	
	<Dolorem>
		<entrance>
		  <person>Welcome to Dolorem, playerName. May your visit be a fortunate one.</person>
    </entrance>
		<History>
      <history>
        Dolorem started out as a small fishing village.
        Basic supplies were within reach, giving the city the chance to grow.
        Villagers would get wood out of Baelin forest, while extracting
        minerals from the quarries in the grey mountains.
        
        Trade routes were set up, making Dolorem an important trade center,
        while staying self-supporting through fishing and agriculture.
      </history>
      <history>
        Due to its coastal location however, defences from attackers
        coming from the seas were low. The city was sacked when the
        Vitharr landed on the coasts in the year 135 of the second era.
        Buildings were set ablaze, men were enslaved, children were 
        slaughtered and left to die in the streets. The once great 
        trade routes were one by one abandoned.
        
        The Vitharr occupied the most of the territory west of the grey
        mountains in a matter of weeks. Led by a wizard, shrouded in mystery,
        they left nothing but burning cinders and despair in their wake.
      </history>
      <history>
        However, one day upon the other, they had disappeared.
        Spectators told of an incoming message, magical of sort some said,
        coming from overseas. Moving at the speed of the wind,
        they had departed just before the break of dawn.
        
        Until this day, over 200 years later, not one can tell exactly
        what had driven the Vitharr away. It has been a tough recovery
        for Dolorem, however.
      </history>
    </History>
    <Conversation>
      <district name="Trade Quarter">
        <person name="John" delay="2000">Say Thomas, have you heard the story about Baelin Woods?</person>
        <person name="Thomas" delay="2000">I don't believe so, what happened?</person>
		<person name="John" delay="3000">My oldest son was playing in the woods at the edge closest to the city, and saw some men seemingly guarding something.</person>
		<person name="Thomas" delay="2000">Must've been something precious to put guards in the woods that close to the city.</person>
		<person name="John" delay="2000">Exactly what I was thinking. To be honest though, I don't have the guts to check it out.</person>
		<person name="Thomas" delay="2000">Might get you into some serious trouble. My curiosity's having a hard time convincing me. Better just leave it be.</person>
      </district>
      <district name="Main Square">
        You hear birds whistling and the river flow in the background.
      </district>
    </Conversation>
	</Dolorem>
	
	<Ferlain>
		<entrance>
		  <person>Ferlain bids you welcome, playerName. I'd like to welcome you in better times, I'm afraid.</person>
		</entrance>
  <History>
		<history>
			Where Dolorem gained profit out of fishing, Ferlain's 
			agricultural strength lies in grain farming.
			The fertile lands between the Western Sea and the grey mountains
			were an ideal foundation for what became the central granary
			for the entire province.
			
			When the Vitharr sweeped the lands,
			the achievements of generations evaporated like water on a hot plate.
			Robbed of its largest source of essential nutrients,
			malnutrition hit the population like a sledgehammer.
		</history>
		<history>
			Although it was quickly contained, insufficient hygiene
			led to disease. The few survivors that were able to escape their
			city's raid, had been hiding in underground crypts.
			During the years preceding the attack, wealthy tradesfamilies
			had built a vast network of tunnels throughout the city.
			
			Quite soon in the early years, competition between kins had evolved 
			into rivalry as Ferlain flourished. Letting a business deal
			slip through their hands, could mean loss of credibility, 
			thereby paving the way for failure, be it on long or short term.
		</history>
		<history>
			Families were in a state of secret war, hiring mercenaries
			to clean up their mess. As personal raids became more frequent,
			escape routes were excavated. Pathways from rivalling kins
			could be as close as a few feet without them even knowing.
			
			When the western lands had turned into an occupied wasteland,
			those tunnels were one of the few chances at survival.
			The owning family would let people in,
			knowing that when it would all be over, the people would be
			one of the most powerful tools in the quest for power.
		</history>
		<history>
			After the destruction, politics were no easy matter.
			Kinships all wanted a piece of the cake of power,
			with rising tensions frequently ending in bloodshed.
			
			However, time is short and work is abundant.
			Should you inquire more information,
			the capital city of Alberin has an extensive library.
		</history>
		</History>
	</Ferlain>
</CityDialog>
