<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!-- New document created with EditiX at Fri Nov 11 10:08:44 CET 2011 -->

<DungeonStrings>
	<forest>
		<day>
			Actually, by day this isn't such a bad place to be, you think.
			As you go deeper into the woods, a strange feeling settles onto you.
			You nearly jump out of your skin as a pheasant shoots through the bushes. Damned birds.
			You see something in the distance. Never mind, it's a tree.
			Regret settles in, with a hunger to destroy entire civilisations. You weren't made to be surrounded by trees.
			It started raining, making what was left of the path you were following a naked mud wrestling paradise. If only..
			For some minutes now, a wretchid stench has been assaulting your nostrils. You stepped in some animal's faeces.
			You remember the townsfolk warning you about going too deep in here. Silly farmers.
			One does not simply jump over this branch like you just did.
			You didn't scare up from seeing for what looked like an evil tree. Everything went better than expected.
		</day>
		<night>
			At night, this isn't such a fun place to be. At all.
			Considering all the things crawling close to, pheasant encounters almost seem like a happy memory.
			Note to self: Carry a torch next time. At least that way you'll see what hits you before it does.
			You've brave, you're bold, you shouldn't be scared.
			You could disappear into a pitfall and no one would be awake to hear you scream.
			The moon gives you some light to see by.
			A bright focused beam of light meets your eye. Someone actually dropped a mirror here, together with some limbs it seems.
			Good Lordy, it sure is dark in here.
			If I'd be a madman, the bloodthirsty howls in the distance would make me feel challenged.
			You just pooped your britches, like a baws.
			You hum the melody the bards would sing as they tale about your epic quest. If you don't die tonight, that is.
			No quiero morir aquí! That's spanish for you being a wimp.
			Perhaps you should just go to sleep.
			Risking your life for glory and fame is overrated.
			Some clouds moved in front of the moon.
			A moist cold enters your feet. Pond you stepped in #257.
		</night>
	</forest>
	<plains>
	  <day>
	  </day>
	  <night>
	  </night>
	</plains>
</DungeonStrings>
